The first call was pretty positive
but then this morning.
the surgeon said they need
to operate again on the leg.
We're on our way there now
before they prep him.
OK. Bye.
For the British? Well...
This man. Ulle Dag Charles.
real name Suleiman.
which he prefers not to use.
understandably.
is an attention-seeking fraud.
Every time he has a new piece
of software to sell.
he promises it will save the world.
but all he wants to do is destroy it.
Ulle Dag Charles is a traitor
to the West and its values.
Bombe!
It's just come in.
I knew you'd wanna see it.
Russian 2000 MG.
Not something you see every day.
Hmm. the serial number's filed off.
Well. terrorists aren't
entirely stupid.
So. is it the genuine article?
Yeah. looks like the real thing.
Although the Brazilian
and Egyptian knock-offs
are almost as good these days.
Very nice gun.
Right. let's see if it's
one of our Belgian dealers.
There's gotta be another one
in here somewhere.
They're not always entirely stupid.
but they're not that smart either.
Bingo.
Have you seen this?
Where is that?
Germany.
That is an absolutely...
beautiful thing.
You know I could have
shipped them to you and. er...
saved you the journey.
What and miss seeing all this?
No. thank you.
Christ. the Puzzle Ball's
something special.
Yes. it is.
Sadly not for sale.
However. I do have
a beautiful Killarney set...
that I might be persuaded to part with.
- Go on then.
- This way.
Christ.
Herr Krasner.
with the greatest respect...
- Mm-hm?
- I need to get out of here
before I bankrupt myself.
Tech entrepreneur. Ulle Dag Charles.
- or UDC as he prefers to be known...
- Hey.
Hey.
- You alright?
- Yeah. I'm good. How are you doing?
Yeah. I'm...
- Yeah.
- Yeah. You want a glass?
No. I'm good. Thank you.
He calls River.
Ulle Dag Charles. what is this
mysterious new software. River?
River is a revolutionary technology...
Er. how's the paper?
I finally came up with
a new title for it. actually.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What is it?
It's called. "Problematic
Violences and Self-Authorship:
Traps of the Messianic and the Tragic."
Thank you.
What does it actually mean. though?
Come on. you learned firearms.
you know what it means.
Where's Jasmine? Homework?
- Homework. exactly.
- Why is a man who is a founder member
of the billionaire club turning
against his fellow billionaires?
Can we find something
on the Fest killing. please?
Come on. this is UDC.
You should be all over this.
He's got like 240 million followers.
- Some people think he's God.
- Yeah. including him.
- Look at him.
- You never know with this guy. though.
I mean. if this software does
what it's supposed to.
it's gonna show us where
all the big money's coming from
and where it goes.
Like. if he pulls this off.
this could get really interesting.
But it's not interesting right now.
Someone's been assassinated.
- It is to me.
- Can you ju...
No! Listen. you can't just come here...
- Give me it.
- Come home... Fine. fine. fine.
Take it. Wow. no respect
for your husband. no?
Thank you.
According to police sources.
Fest was struck by a single bullet
fired by a sniper from long range.
It's not yet confirmed if authorities
have been able
to locate a suspect or...
- Evening. Mum.
- Hi. how you doing?
- How was school?
- Good.
Good. Good.
Do you remember what's
happening tomorrow night?
Yes.
Parent-teachers' evening.
Yes. Yes. I'm going to come.
- Good.
- Alright?
- OK.
- Was visiting his son.
Elias Fest.
at the Saint Elizabeth hospital.
who had suffered injuries
the day prior.
I offered. She wants you.
A connection
between these incidents.
forming a broader conspiracy
against the Fest family.
- Passport.
- Ja.
Do you know. this is the first time
that I've ever been asked
for a passport crossing
between Germany and France.
- Where are you coming from?
- Er. Nuremberg.
Do you live in Nuremberg?
- Er. no. I live in Paris.
- What were you doing in Nuremberg?
I was visiting someone on business.
- Is this your car?
- No. it's a rental.
Open the boot.
Open it. please.
What's happening here?
Nothing to worry about.
What's in the box?
Ah. so this...
is why I was in Nuremberg.
This...
is a Jaques set.
The ivory is all pre-ban.
And it's. er... it's incredibly rare.
I collect these things.
Wait here.
- You can go.
- Thank you very much.
Have a great evening.
Thank you.
What's the latest on the Fest shooting?
Er. the report's
literally just come in.
Should be on your screen now.
Single shot to the head.
A lot of splatter.
Bloody good shot.
- No. that can't be right.
- What?
3.815 metres.
But that... that's not possible.
Well. it's what the Germans are saying.
And we know how precise
the Germans are.
- What's-What's going on?
- They've called a meeting about it.
Osi. Osi.
I should be at the Fest meeting.
- You'll get a full briefing afterwards.
- No. no. no. no.
I don't want a full briefing.
Snipers is my patch.
- I didn't draw up the names. Bianca.
- Well. wait. wait. wait.
- Who did? Was it Isabel?
- I assume so.
Well... Look. Jordan's in there.
Jordan.
What does Jordan know about snipers?
I have to be in there.
Who is that anyway?
Werner Leckner. German Intelligence.
Last night there were arson attacks
on mosques in Hamburg.
Berlin and Dresden.
And there's been rioting
in different parts of the country.
It's obviously very alarming. Werner.
And as you know. the Foreign Secretary
was a personal friend of the Fest
family. He's very shocked.
As are we all.
What do you need from us?
We are not making any assumptions
about the nationality of the sniper.
so we are reaching out to all
our international partners
for assistance.
There's been a lot of speculation
about the shot.
Do you have a confirmed distance?
Yes. indeed. um...
From the apartment block
where the shot was taken
to the hospital door
where Fest was hit is.
er... 3.815 metres.
Are you sure about that?
Because the world record for
a confirmed kill with a sniper rifle
is 3.540 metres.
Ukraine. 2023.
- Did you retrieve the weapon?
- No.
Right. so the sniper took it with him.
This is the suspect leaving
the apartment building.
two minutes and 52 seconds
after the shot was fired.
But... er. sorry. where's the rifle?
He broke it down and put it
in the bag. Obviously.
Can we get dimensions. please?
The bag is less
than 60 centimetres tall.
- So?
- The Tac-50 barrel is 737 millimetres
and it's the shortest around
in this category.
The Denel barrel is a full metre long.
The... the... the rifle's
not in the bag.
If it was in the bag.
we'd see the barrel poking out.
He left it behind.
No. forensics found no trace
of a weapon at the scene.
When a sniper finds a rifle.
one that allows him
to make a shot at that distance.
that rifle is a keeper.
He's never going to leave it behind.
Which means he took it with him.
And if he took it with him.
then it has to be in that bag.
I'm not following. Bianca.
You said the bag isn't big enough?
Which means the rifle is bespoke.
- The barrel came in two parts.
- A...
barrel in two parts is
the gunmaker's holy grail.
If the rifling were out
the tiniest fraction.
it would compromise the shot.
It's impossible.
There's a gunmaker who's been
trying to do this for years.
His name is Norman Stoke.
Is Mr Stoke British?
- Northern Irish.
- Well...
I suppose they count as British.
for now.
Do we know where Mr Stoke is?
Can we get Special Branch
to scoop him up?
He's been on the run since
the Stockholm assassination in 2018.
- How unfortunate.
- But I have an asset.
I know I can find him.
What good would that do us?
Oh. well. gunmaker makes gun.
Gunmaker sells gun to assassin.
- Highly speculative.
- It is a lead. however.
And. to be frank.
we don't have many of those.
- Bonjour.
Bianca. A moment. please.
It's always flattering
when the Germans come asking
for our expertise.
Although it would be
a little embarrassing
if the gunmaker turns out
to be British.
Who exactly is this Norman Stoke?
Stoke started making machine-guns
for loyalist paramilitaries
back in the '80s in East Belfast.
Norman and his brother Larry.
killed more than a dozen
innocent Catholic civilians.
Larry was eventually caught
and went to prison
but was released
under the peace agreement.
Er. he's now an enforcer
for a gang of drug dealers.
Norman. meanwhile. perfected his craft
and made the gun used
in the Stockholm assassination.
How would you go about
finding Norman Stoke?
I have an asset in Belfast.
Codename: Sparrow.
I've heard good things
about you. Bianca.
Don't let me down.
Yeah.
- Hey.
You look like you're at an airport.
- Yeah. sorry.
- But what about parents' evening?
So. I'm assuming you're not coming?
It's a last-minute thing.
You know. she's really
worked her socks off this term.
I know. I know. I feel awful about
it. There was nothing I could do.
Well. you could try
telling her yourself?
Paul. I can't. I can't.
I-I've just got to Belfast
and I'm-I'm already late for a meeting.
- Right. OK.
- Can you do it. please?
- OK.
- Look. I will try my best
to get on the last flight.
- OK.
- OK?
- I'm sorry.
- Alright. bye. bye.
OK. bye.
When I saw your number.
I almost had a stroke.
Thought I'd seen the last of you.
It has been a long time.
How've you been?
- What do you want. Nadine?
- How's the family?
Leave my family out of it.
If Larry knew who I was talking to.
he'd kill me.
There you go. Thanks ever so much.
Do come back and see us.
Have a good day.
But you're being careful?
You remember the protocols?
- Yes.
- Good.
Then there's nothing
for you to worry about.
When was the last time Larry
spoke to his brother Norman?
Not since he disappeared.
Are you telling me the truth. Alison?
I know the brothers are close
and I need to find Norman now.
Not my problem.
It's very much your problem.
because if you don't help me
find Norman.
you'll go back to prison.
Are you married?
- No.
- Children?
- Nope.
- Career woman.
It's written all over you.
If you had a husband. you'd know
men have their little secrets.
Well. this is a little secret
I want in on.
I need you to find out
where Norman is... today.
I can't just ask Larry out the blue.
He'll be suspicious.
I'd have to work up to it.
You've got my number.
I expect to hear from you tonight.
Can I go now?
It's a free country.
This is Alison. Leave a message.
Alison. it's Nadine.
I haven't heard from you
and I'm very disappointed. Call me.
Nadine?
Oh. office in-joke.
Look. baby. I'm so sorry.
You know. about parents' evening.
I really am.
Don't turn around.
Did you come alone?
Yes. I followed
your instructions to the letter.
Who's the target?
Ulle Dag Charles. UDC.
Can you get to him?
It'll cost.
I mentioned a guide price
of ten million dollars.
Multiply that by ten and then
perhaps we can have a conversation.
That's a very expensive conversation.
Half on commission. half on completion.
All reasonable expenses paid.
Well. I'd have to consult
my colleagues about that.
Hello?
Alison. it's Nadine. You were
supposed to call me last night.
I need to hear from you.
Er. get me everything we have
on Alison's daughter. Emma.
- Copy.
- Yeah?
Yeah. yeah. On it.
The BND believe. er...
The BND believe our sniper
thought he'd find Manfred
at the Fest Und Fest Unternehmen
offices the night before.
But Manfred wasn't there
so he shot his son. Elias.
Manfred was always the real target.
Elias was used as bait
to lure Manfred to the hospital.
That would take a lot of pre-planning.
Well. all planning is pre.
How did Belfast go?
My asset isn't cooperating.
I think we have to get
creative on this one.
She has a daughter. Emma.
A student in London.
Involved in a radical leftist group.
I think I can see where
you're going with this.
We have to be very careful
about sanctioning
this kind of operation.
UDC! UDC! UDC! UDC!
- What do we want?!
- The truth about money!
- When do we want it?
- Now!
UDC! UDC! UDC!
River's here to make it clear!
You can't wash your money here!
UDC! UDC! UDC! UDC!
Yep. that's her in the pink scarf.
Do I have to wait for her to act up?
No. Just go get her.
Fine by me.
Miss. you're causing
an obstruction in a public highway.
If you do not get up and move
right now. you're liable for arrest.
Why don't you go
and do something useful
like arrest the fat cats...
You can't wash your money here!
- I'm not threatening you. miss.
- Well. OK. well you should try
being where I am...
That's a threat. It's a threat to me.
I'm being reasonable.
I'm not raising my voice
in the way that you are.
I don't care about your law.
I don't care!
Right. that's enough.
Have 'em up. Thank you!
Get your hands off me. lackey!
- Whose streets?!
- Our streets!
You're in very serious trouble. Emma.
You're in very serious trouble.
We have four witnesses who saw you
throw the bottle at the police officer.
We got four...
witnesses who saw you throw the bottle
at the police officer.
What bottle?
What are you talking about?
Nobody was throwing anything.
You didn't even ask about the officer.
- She was badly hurt.
- I didn't throw any bottle.
The officer's gonna lose her right eye.
She's gonna lose her right eye.
since you didn't ask.
Just a young woman.
doing her job.
How's that make you feel. Emma?
You're making this up.
So fuck right off.
And I want a solicitor.
I have a right to a solicitor.
You can call your mother.
This way. please.
- Fuck off me!
- Get in there.
Where's my solicitor?!
Where's my solicitor?! This is illegal!
Oh. my God!
I wasn't expecting you until next week.
What and miss Carlito's birthday?
Not happening.
- Talk to me.
- She was like this when I found her.
She's still alive.
I've called the paramedics.
"At the tone.
please record your message."
Bianca.
we've got a serious problem
with your student.
- What the fuck is going on?
- She collapsed.
They think it's a cardiac issue.
They've stabilised her.
They think she's gonna make it.
I'm the accompanying officer.
Emma. Hang on. OK?
You're gonna be alright.
What's happening?
She's arrested.
- I'm gonna shock her.
- Let me help.
Charging.
Stand clear! Shocking.